Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Articles File
        - Kane, J(ames) Herbert (Box 15, Folder 1642)
        - karrer, Otto (Box 15, Folder 1643)
        - Kasatkin, Nikolai (Box 15, Folder 1644)
        - kats, Wilma (Box 15, Folder 1645)
        - kaundinya, Hermann (Box 15, Folder 1646)
        - Kaur, Rajkumari Amrit (Not included in Dictionnary) (Box 15, Folder 1647)
        - Keasberry, Benjamin Peach (Box 15, Folder 1648)
        - Keith-Falconer, Ion Grant Neville (Box 15, Folder 1649)
        - Keller, Otto and Marian (Box 15, Folder 1650)
        - Kekela, James (Box 15, Folder 1651)
        - Kellersberger, Eugene Roland (Box 15, Folder 1652)
        - Kelley, Francis Clement (Box 15, Folder 1653)
        - Kemp, Johannes Theodorus (Box 15, Folder 1654)
        - Kemper, John and Mabel (Box 15, Folder 1655)
        - Kendall, Thomas (Box 15, Folder 1656)
        - Kentigern (Box 15, Folder 1657)
        - Keough, George D. (Box 15, Folder 1658)
        - Kepler, A. R. (Box 15, Folder 1659)
        - Kerr, George McGlashan (Box 15, Folder 1660)
        - Kerr, John Glasgow (Box 15, Folder 1661)
        - Kersten, Christoph (Box 15, Folder 1662)
        - Kevin, Mother (Box 15, Folder 1663)
        - Keysser, Christian (Box 15, Folder 1664)
        - Khama III (Box 15, Folder 1665)
        - Khrisanf, Shchetkovsky (Box 15, Folder 1666)
        - Kidder, Daniel P. (Box 15, Folder 1667)
        - Kidder, Mary (Box 15, Folder 1668)
        - Kiernander, John Zachary (Box 15, Folder 1669)
        - Kigozi, Blasio (Box 15, Folder 1670)
        - Kijne, I (Box 15, Folder 1671)
        - Kilbourne, Edwin (Box 15, Folder 1672)
        - Kilger, Laurenz (Box 15, Folder 1673)
        - Kilham, Hannah (Box 15, Folder 1674)
        - Kilian (Kyllena) (Box 15, Folder 1675)
        - Kim, Andrew Tae kon (Box 15, Folder 1676)
        - Kim, Andrew (Box 15, Folder 1677)
        - kim, Helen (Box 15, Folder 1678)
        - Kimbangu, Simon (Box 15, Folder 1679)
        - Kincaid, Eugenio (Box 15, Folder 1680)
        - King, Clifford (Box 15, Folder 1681)
        - King, Copland (Box 15, Folder 1682)
        - King, Johnnes (Box 15, Folder 1683)
        - King, Jonas (Box 15, Folder 1684)
        - Kingsbury, Cyrus (Box 15, Folder 1685)
        - Kino, Eusebio Francisco (Box 15, Folder 1686)
        - Kinsolving, Lucien Lee (Box 15, Folder 1687)
        - Klein, Frederick A. (Box 15, Folder 1688)
        - Kleinschmidt, J. C. (Box 15, Folder 1689)
        - Klinkert, H. C. (Box 15, Folder 1690)
        - knak, Seigfried (Box 16, Folder 1691)
        - knibb, William (Box 16, Folder 1692)
        - Knight-Bruce, G. W H. (Box 16, Folder 1693)
        - Knoblecher, Ignaz (Box 16, Folder 1694)
        - Knox, Eleanor (Box 16, Folder 1695)
        - Ko Tha Byu (Box 16, Folder 1696)
        - Kobes, Alois (Box 16, Folder 1697)
        - Koechlin, Alphonse (Box 16, Folder 1698)
        - Koelle, Sigismund Wilhelm (Box 16, Folder 1699)
        - Koo, T. Z. (Box 16, Folder 1700)
        - Kowalsky, Nikolaus (Box 16, Folder 1701)
        - koyi, William Mtusane (Box 16, Folder 1702)
        - Kreamer, Hendrik (Box 16, Folder 1703)
        - Kraus, Johannes (Box 16, Folder 1704)
        - Krapf, Johann Ludwig (Box 16, Folder 1705)
        - Krawielitzki, Theophil (Box 16, Folder 1706)
        - Krige, Jacob Daniel (Empty) (Box 16, Folder 1707)
        - Krishna Pillai, (Henry Alfred) (Box 16, Folder 1708)
        - Kruyt, Albertus Christian (Box 16, Folder 1709)
        - Kuder, John (Box 16, Folder 1710)
        - Kugler, Ann Sarah (Box 16, Folder 1711)
        - Kuhn, Isobel Miller (Box 16, Folder 1712)
        - Kuksha (Box 16, Folder 1713)
        - Kuscha (Box 16, Folder 1714)
        - Kulp, H. Stover (Box 16, Folder 1715)
        - Kumm, Hermann Karl Wilhelm and Lucy Evangeline (Guinness) (Box 16, Folder 1716)
        - Lacombe, Albert (Box 16, Folder 1717)
        - Lacroix, Alphonse Francois (Box 16, Folder 1718)
        - Lafitau, Joseph Francoise (Box 16, Folder 1719)
        - Laiser, Lazarus (Box 16, Folder 1720)
        - Lake, John Graham (Box 16, Folder 1721)
        - Lalande, Jean de (Box 16, Folder 1722)
        - Lalemant (L'Allemant) Gabriel (Box 16, Folder 1723)
        - Lalemant, Jerome (Achiedasse) (Box 16, Folder 1724)
        - Lambert de la Motte, Pierre (Box 16, Folder 1725)
        - Lambie, Thomas A. (Box 16, Folder 1726)
        - Lamburn, George Patrick (Box 16, Folder 1727)
        - Lambuth, Walter (Box 16, Folder 1728)
        - Lanneau, Sophie (Box 16, Folder 1729)
        - Lapsley, Samuel H. (Box 16, Folder 1730)
        - Larsen, Lars Peter (Box 16, Folder 1731)
        - Larson, Ruben (Box 16, Folder 1732)
        - La Salle, John Baptist de (Box 16, Folder 1733)
        - Las Casas, Bartolome de (Box 16, Folder 1734)
        - Latourette, Kenneth Scott (Box 16, Folder 1735)
        - Laubach, Frank Charles (Box 16, Folder 1736)
        - Laufer, Carl (Box 16, Folder 1737)
        - Launay, Adrien (Box 16, Folder 1738)
        - Laurie, Thomas (Box 16, Folder 1739)
        - Lavigerie, Charles Martial Allemand (Box 16, Folder 1740)
        - Laval, Jacques Desire (Box 16, Folder 1741)
        - Lawes, William George (Box 16, Folder 1742)
        - Lawrence, Edward A. (Box 16, Folder 1743)
        - Laws, Robert (Box 16, Folder 1744)
        - Leander of Serville (Box 16, Folder 1745)
        - Lebbe, Vincent-Frederic-Marie (Box 16, Folder 1746)
        - Leber, Charles (Box 16, Folder 1747)
        - Lebuin (Lebwin) (Box 16, Folder 1748)
        - Lechler, Paul (Box 16, Folder 1749)
        - Lechler, Rudolf (Box 16, Folder 1750)
        - Le Comte, Louis (Box 16, Folder 1751)
        - Le Roux, Petrus Louis (Box 16, Folder 1752)
        - Le Roy, Alexander (Box 16, Folder 1753)
        - Le Saux, Henri (Box 16, Folder 1754)
        - Ledochowska, Maria Theresia (Box 16, Folder 1755)
        - Lee, Daniel (Box 16, Folder 1756)
        - Lee, Jason (Box 16, Folder 1757)
        - Ledochwski, Wladimir (Box 16, Folder 1758)
        - Ledyard, Gleason (Box 16, Folder 1760)
        - Lenkeevich, Nikolai (Box 16, Folder 1761)
        - Leenhardt, Maurice (Box 16, Folder 1762)
        - Leeuwen, Arend Th. Van (Box 16, Folder 1763)
        - Lefroy, George A. (Box 16, Folder 1764)
        - Legge, James (Box 16, Folder 1765)
        - Legge, Mary Isabelle (Box 16, Folder 1766)
        - Lehmann, Arno (Box 16, Folder 1767)
        - Leibniz, Gottfried (Box 16, Folder 1768)
        - Leimena, J. (Box 16, Folder 1769)
        - Leite, Serafim (Box 16, Folder 1770)
        - Le Jeune, Paul (Box 16, Folder 1771)
        - Lemue, Prosper (Box 16, Folder 1772)
        - Lemmens, Lonard (Box 16, Folder 1773)
        - Lenkeevich, Nicodim (Box 16, Folder 1774)
        - Lenshina, Alice (Box 16, Folder 1775)
        - Leontiev, Maxim (Box 16, Folder 1776)
        - Lepsius, Johannes (Box 16, Folder 1777)
        - Lery, Jean de (Box 16, Folder 1778)
        - Leszczinski, Filofei (Box 16, Folder 1779)
        - Leupolt, Charles Benjamin (Box 16, Folder 1780)
        - Lew, Timothy Tingfang (Box 16, Folder 1781)
        - Lewis, Marianne (Box 16, Folder 1782)
        - Lewis, Thomas (Box 16, Folder 1783)
        - Leydecker, Melchior (Box 16, Folder 1784)
        - Liang Fa (Box 16, Folder 1785)
        - Libermann, Francois Marie Paul (Box 16, Folder 1786)
        - Li Chih Tsao (Li Zhizao) (Box 16, Folder 1787)
        - Lichtenstein, Isaac (Box 16, Folder 1788)
        - Liddell, Eric (Box 16, Folder 1789)
        - Lieberkuhn, Samuel (Box 16, Folder 1790)
        - Liele, George (Box 16, Folder 1791)
        - Lievens, Constantin (Box 16, Folder 1792)
        - Ligget, Thomas J. (Box 17, Folder 1793)
        - Liggins, John (Box 17, Folder 1794)
        - Lajadu, Emmanuel Moses (Box 17, Folder 1795)
        - Lijadu (or Lidaju?) (Box 17, Folder 1796)
        - Limbrock, Eberhard Micheal (Box 17, Folder 1797)
        - Lindell, Jonathan Luther (Box 17, Folder 1798)
        - Lindley, Daniel (Box 17, Folder 1799)
        - Lindsay,Gordon and Freda Theresa (Schimpf) (Box 17, Folder 1800)
        - Lioba (Box 17, Folder 1801)
        - Lith, Franciscus Van (Box 17, Folder 1802)
        - Litwiller, John T.N. (Box 17, Folder 1803)
        - Livinhac, Leon (Box 17, Folder 1804)
        - Little, Paul (Box 17, Folder 1805)
        - Livingstone, David (Box 17, Folder 1806)
        - Livingston, Mary Moffat (Box 17, Folder 1807)
        - Llinas, Antonio (Box 17, Folder 1808)
        - Lloyed, Arthur (Box 17, Folder 1809)
        - Loayza, Geronimo de (Box 17, Folder 1810)
        - Lock, Annie (Box 17, Folder 1811)
        - Lockhart, William (Box 17, Folder 1812)
        - Lohe, Johann Konrad Wilhelm (Box 17, Folder 1813)
        - Lohmann, Ernst (Box 17, Folder 1814)
        - Lohr, Oscar (Box 17, Folder 1815)
        - Lombard, Eva (Box 17, Folder 1816)
        - Long, James (Box 17, Folder 1817)
        - (Long), Retta Dixon (Box 17, Folder 1818)
        - Longinus (Box 17, Folder 1819)
        - Lopez, Gregorio (Lo Wen-tsao) (Box 17, Folder 1820)
        - Lopez de Mendoza Grajales, Francisco (See also Grajales) (Box 17, Folder 1821)
        - Lorenz, Henry W. (Box 17, Folder 1822)
        - Lorrain, James Herbert (Box 17, Folder 1823)
        - Losada, Jorgelina (Box 17, Folder 1824)
        - Lourdel, Simeon (Box 17, Folder 1825)
        - Louw, Andries Adriaan (Box 17, Folder 1826)
        - Love, John (Box 17, Folder 1827)
        - Loveless, Sarah (Box 17, Folder 1828)
        - Lowe, Gentry G. (Box 17, Folder 1829)
        - Lowrie, John C. (Box 17, Folder 1830)
        - Lowry, Gentry G. (Box 17, Folder 1831)
        - Lubac, Henry de (Box 17, Folder 1832)
        - Lucas, Benard (Box 17, Folder 1833)
        - Lucas, William Vincent (Box 17, Folder 1834)
        - Luce, Henry Winters (Box 17, Folder 1835)
        - Luce, Alice Eveline (Box 17, Folder 1836)
        - Ludger (Box 17, Folder 1837)
        - Lugo, Juan L. (Box 17, Folder 1838)
        - Lull, Raymond (also Llull, or Lullus Raiundus) (Box 17, Folder 1839)
        - Luquet, Jean Felix Onesime (Box 17, Folder 1840)
        - Luther, Martin (Box 17, Folder 1841)
        - Luthuli, Albert John Mvumbi (Box 17, Folder 1842)
        - Lukens, Franz (Box 17, Folder 1843)
        - Luzbetak, Louis J. (Box 17, Folder 1844)
        - Lyall, Leslie Theodore (Box 17, Folder 1845)
        - Lyman, David B. (Box 17, Folder 1846)
        - Lyon, D. Willard (Box 17, Folder 1847)
        - Lyons, Lorenzo (Box 17, Folder 1848)
        - Lyon, Mary (Box 17, Folder 1849)
        - Ma, Xiangbo (Box 17, Folder 1850)
        - Maas, Otto (Box 17, Folder 1851)
        - Mabie, Catherine Louise Roe (Box 17, Folder 1852)
        - Mabille, Adolph and Adele (Casalis) (Box 17, Folder 1853)
        - MacCallum, Lyman (Box 17, Folder 1854)
        - MacDonald, Alexander (Box 17, Folder 1855)
        - MacDonald, Andrew Buchanan (Box 17, Folder 1856)
        - MacDonald, A(nnie) Caroline (Box 17, Folder 1857)
        - MacDonald, Duff (Box 17, Folder 1858)
        - MacDonald, Ducan Black (Box 17, Folder 1859)
        - MacFarlane, Samuel (Box 17, Folder 1860)
        - MacGillivray, D. (Box 17, Folder 1861)
        - Macgowan, Edward (Box 17, Folder 1862)
        - Machray, Robert (Box 17, Folder 1863)
        - Mack, (Johann) Martin (Box 17, Folder 1864)
        - Mackay, Alxander M. (Box 17, Folder 1865)
        - Mack, John (Box 17, Folder 1866)
        - Mackay, George Leslie (Box 17, Folder 1867)
        - Mackay, John Alexander (Box 17, Folder 1868)
        - Mackenzie, Charles Frederick (Box 17, Folder 1869)
        - Makenzie, Helen (Box 17, Folder 1870)
        - Mackenzie, Jean Kenyon (Box 17, Folder 1871)
        - Mackenzie, John (Box 17, Folder 1872)
        - Mackenzie, John Kenneth (Box 17, Folder 1873)
        - Mackichan, Dugald (Box 17, Folder 1874)
        - Mackie, Robert (Box 17, Folder 1875)
        - Maclaren, Albert (Box 17, Folder 1876)
        - Maclay, Robert S. (Box 17, Folder 1877)
        - Macnicol, Nicol (Box 17, Folder 1878)
        - Macvicar, Neil (Box 17, Folder 1879)
        - Magee, John G. (Box 17, Folder 1880)
        - Maigrot, Charles (Box 17, Folder 1881)
        - Mailla, Joseph Marie-Anne Moyriac de (Box 17, Folder 1882)
        - Main, Ducan (Box 17, Folder 1883)
        - Makarii of Attai (Box 17, Folder 1884)
        - Makarii Altaiskii (Box 17, Folder 1885)
        - Makarius, Glukharev (also Glucharjew), Michael (Box 17, Folder 1886)
        - Makemie, Francis (Box 17, Folder 1887)
        - Makkai, Sandor (Box 17, Folder 1888)
        - Maldonado (Box 17, Folder 1889)
        - Malinki, James M. (Box 17, Folder 1890)
        - Malpan, Abraham (Box 17, Folder 1891)
        - Mamora, Lucius (Box 17, Folder 1892)
        - Manikam, Rajah B. (Box 17, Folder 1893)
        - Manna, Paola (Box 17, Folder 1894)
        - Manso, Alonso (Box 17, Folder 1895)
        - Maranke, John (Box 17, Folder 1896)
        - Maretu (Box 17, Folder 1897)
        - Margil, Antonio (Box 17, Folder 1898)
        - Marie de I'Assomption (Marie Le Roy Ladurie) (Box 17, Folder 1899)
        - Markey, John (Box 17, Folder 1900)
        - Margull, Hans-Jochen (Box 17, Folder 1901)
        - Marie of the Incarnation (Marie Guyard) (Box 17, Folder 1902)
        - Marks, John Ebenezer (Box 18, Folder 1903)
        - Marmoiton, Blaise (Box 18, Folder 1904)
        - Marquette, Jacques (Box 18, Folder 1905)
        - Marsden, Samuel (Box 18, Folder 1906)
        - Martin, William Alexander Parsons (Box 18, Folder 1907)
        - Marshman, Hannah (Box 18, Folder 1908)
        - Marshman, John C. (Box 18, Folder 1909)
        - Marshman, Joshua (Box 18, Folder 1910)
        - Marston, Sarah Hall (Box 18, Folder 1911)
        - Martin, Marie-Louis (Box 18, Folder 1912)
        - Martin, Frederick (Box 18, Folder 1913)
        - Martin of Tour (Box 18, Folder 1914)
        - Martini, Martino (Box 18, Folder 1915)
        - Martines, Francesco (Box 18, Folder 1916)
        - Martinez de Companon, Baltasar Jaime (Box 18, Folder 1917)
        - Martinez, Pedro (Box 18, Folder 1918)
        - Marty, Martin (Box 18, Folder 1919)
        - Martyn, Henry (Box 18, Folder 1920)
        - Massanet, Damian (Box 18, Folder 1921)
        - Mason, Francis (Box 18, Folder 1922)
        - Massaja, Guglielmo (Box 18, Folder 1923)
        - Massignon, Louis (Box 18, Folder 1924)
        - Masson, Josef (Box 18, Folder 1925)
        - Mateer, Calvin Wilson (Box 18, Folder 1926)
        - Mather, Cotton (Box 18, Folder 1927)
        - Mather, Percy Cunningham (Box 18, Folder 1928)
        - Mather, Robert Cotton and Wife (Box 18, Folder 1929)
        - Mattews, Daniel (and Janet) (Box 18, Folder 1930)
        - Matthews, Luke (Box 18, Folder 1931)
        - Matthews, Thomas Trotter (Box 18, Folder 1932)
        - Matthews, Z(achariah) (Box 18, Folder 1933)
        - Matthopoulos, Eusebius (Box 18, Folder 1934)
        - Maturana, Magarita Maria (Box 18, Folder 1935)
        - Maunsell, Robert (Box 18, Folder 1936)
        - Mayhew, Experience (Box 18, Folder 1937)
        - Mayhew, Thomas, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 1938)
        - Mazenod, Charles-Joseph-Eugene (Box 18, Folder 1939)
        - Mazzuchelli, Samuel (Box 18, Folder 1940)
        - McBeth, Sue (Box 18, Folder 1941)
        - McCall, Alexander (Box 18, Folder 1942)
        - McCandlisse, Henry M., M.D. (Box 18, Folder 1943)
        - McCartee, Davie Bethune (Box 18, Folder 1944)
        - McClure, Donald (Box 18, Folder 1945)
        - MacCoy, Issac (Box 18, Folder 1946)
        - McDonald, Robert (Box 18, Folder 1947)
        - McDougall, Francis Thomas (Box 18, Folder 1948)
        - McDowell, Henry Curtis (Box 18, Folder 1949)
        - MacDowell, Robert (Box 18, Folder 1950)
        - McFarland, Samuel Gamble (Box 18, Folder 1951)
        - MacGavran, Donald Anderson (Box 18, Folder 1952)
        - McGilvary, Daniel (Box 18, Folder 1953)
        - McKechnie, E. M. (Box 18, Folder 1954)
        - McLaurin, John (Box 18, Folder 1955)
        - McLaurin, John Bates (Box 18, Folder 1956)
        - McPherson, Aimee Semple (Box 18, Folder 1957)
        - Mebius, Federick W. (Box 18, Folder 1958)
        - Medhurst, Walter Henry (Box 18, Folder 1959)
        - Meeuwsen, Johanna (Box 18, Folder 1960)
        - Megapolensis, Johannes (Box 18, Folder 1961)
        - Mel, Conrad (Box 18, Folder 1962)
        - Melrose, Margaret Rae (Box 18, Folder 1963)
        - Men, Aleksander (Box 18, Folder 1964)
        - Menard, Rene (Box 18, Folder 1965)
        - Mendes, Alphonsus (Box 18, Folder 1966)
        - Mendieta, Jeronimo (Box 18, Folder 1967)
        - Meinhof, Carl (Box 18, Folder 1968)
        - Menzes, Aleixode (Meneses, Alejo de) (Box 18, Folder 1969)
        - Merensky, Alexander (Box 18, Folder 1970)
        - Merrick, James L. (Box 18, Folder 1971)
        - Mesrob (Box 18, Folder 1972)
        - Merwe, William J. Van der (Box 18, Folder 1973)
        - Methodius (Box 18, Folder 1974)
        - Meyendorff, John (Box 18, Folder 1975)
        - Meyer, Louis (Box 18, Folder 1977)
        - Meyer, Lucy Jane Rider (Box 18, Folder 1978)
        - Meyer, Theodore J. (Box 18, Folder 1979)
        - Mezzabarba, Carlo (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 1980)
        - Middleton, Thomas Fanshaw (Box 18, Folder 1981)
        - Millar, Robert (Box 18, Folder 1982)
        - Miller, Harry W. (Box 18, Folder 1983)
        - Miller William (Box 18, Folder 1984)
        - Miller, Wiliam McElwee (Box 18, Folder 1985)
        - Miller, Walter Rchard S. (Box 18, Folder 1986)
        - Miller, William R. S. (Box 18, Folder 1987)
        - Mills, Samuel John Jr. (Box 18, Folder 1988)
        - Mills, W(ilson) Plumer (Box 18, Folder 1989)
        - Milman, Robert (Box 18, Folder 1990)
        - Millne, Andre Murray (Box 18, Folder 1991)
        - Milne, Rachel (Box 18, Folder 1992)
        - Milne, William (Box 18, Folder 1993)
        - Minchen, C. H. (Box 18, Folder 1994)
        - Miner, Louella (Box 18, Folder 1995)
        - Mingo, Wang (Box 18, Folder 1996)
        - Mingo de la Concepcion, Manuel (Box 18, Folder 1997)
        - Mirbt, Carl (Box 18, Folder 1998)
        - Misley, Sandor Nee Rozsa Puchlin (Box 18, Folder 1999)
        - Mitchell, John Murray (Box 18, Folder 2000)
        - Mizeki, B enard (Box 18, Folder 2001)
        - Moe, Malla (Box 18, Folder 2002)
        - Moegling, Hermann Friedrich (Box 18, Folder 2003)
        - Moelia, T. S. G. (Box 18, Folder 2004)
        - Moffat, J. Smith (Box 18, Folder 2005)
        - Moffat, Robert and Mary (Box 18, Folder 2006)
        - Moffett, Samuel Austin (Box 18, Folder 2007)
        - Moffett, Samuel Hugh (Box 19, Folder 2008)
        - Moirans,Epifanio de (Box 19, Folder 2009)
        - Mokone, Mangena Maake (Box 19, Folder 2010)
        - Molnar, Maria (Box 19, Folder 2011)
        - Monchanin, Jules (Box 19, Folder 2012)
        - Mondreganes, Pio M. de (Box 19, Folder 2013)
        - Money, Herbert (Box 19, Folder 2014)
        - Monguiardino, Jose (Box 19, Folder 2015)
        - Moninger, (Mary) Margaret (Box 19, Folder 2016)
        - Monnier, Henri (Box 19, Folder 2017)
        - Monsen, Marie (Box 19, Folder 2018)
        - Montalbin, Francisco (Box 19, Folder 2019)
        - Montesino(s), Antonio de (Box 19, Folder 2020)
        - Montgomery, Henry Hutchinson (Box 19, Folder 2021)
        - Montgomery, Helen Barrett (Box 19, Folder 2022)
        - Moody, Campbell Naismith (Box 19, Folder 2023)
        - Moody, Dwight Lyman (Box 19, Folder 2024)
        - Moomaw, Ira W. (Box 19, Folder 2025)
        - Moon, Charlotte Diggs ("Lottie") (Box 19, Folder 2026)
        - Moore, Joanna Patterson (Box 19, Folder 2027)
        - Moorshead, Robert Fletcher (Box 19, Folder 2028)
        - Moreau, Basil Anthony (Box 19, Folder 2029)
        - Morales Juan Bautista de (Box 19, Folder 2030)
        - Morris, John Webster (Box 19, Folder 2031)
        - Morris, William Case (Box 19, Folder 2032)
        - Marrison, Mary (Box 19, Folder 2033)
        - Morrison, Robert (Box 19, Folder 2034)
        - Morrison, William M. (Box 19, Folder 2035)
        - Morse, Jedidiah (Box 19, Folder 2036)
        - Moshoeshoe (Box 19, Folder 2037)
        - Moses, David G. (Box 19, Folder 2038)
        - Motolinia (Box 19, Folder 2039)
        - Mott, John R. (Box 19, Folder 2040)
        - Motta, Waldomiro (Box 19, Folder 2041)
        - Moule, Arthur Evans (Box 19, Folder 2042)
        - Moule, George Evans (Mention brothers also) (Box 19, Folder 2043)
        - Moulton, Ebenezer (Box 19, Folder 2044)
        - Mouly, Joseph Martial (Box 19, Folder 2045)
        - Moye de Contreras, Pedro (Box 19, Folder 2046)
        - Moye, Jean Martin (Box 19, Folder 2047)
        - Muir, William (mention brother John also) (Box 19, Folder 2048)
        - Mukhia, David (Box 19, Folder 2049)
        - Mulder, Alfonsus Joannes Maria (Box 19, Folder 2050)
        - Mullens, Joseph and Hannah (Box 19, Folder 2051)
        - Muller, George (Box 19, Folder 2052)
        - Muller, Karl (Box 19, Folder 2053)
        - Murdoch, John (Box 19, Folder 2054)
        - Murray, Andrew Jr. (Box 19, Folder 2055)
        - Murray, Andrew Sr. (Box 19, Folder 2056)
        - Murray, Archibald Wright (Box 19, Folder 2057)
        - Murray, W. H. (Box 19, Folder 2058)
        - Murray, William (Box 19, Folder 2059)
        - Murillo Velardo, Pedro (Box 19, Folder 2060)
        - Mutendi, Samuel (Box 19, Folder 2061)
        - Muthiah, Narayana (Box 19, Folder 2062)
        - Myers, Estella (Box 19, Folder 2063)
        - Myklebust, Olav Guttorm (Box 19, Folder 2064)
        - Nacquart, Charles (Box 19, Folder 2065)
        - Nagenda, william (Box 19, Folder 2066)
        - Nakada, Juji (Box 19, Folder 2067)
        - Nankyamas, Theodore (Box 19, Folder 2068)
        - Nanpei, Henry (Box 19, Folder 2069)
        - Nassau, Robert Hamill (Box 19, Folder 2070)
        - Naude, Christiaan Frederick Beyers (Box 19, Folder 2071)
        - Navarrete, Domingo (Box 19, Folder 2072)
        - Nee, Henry (Watchman) (Ni Tuo-Sheng) (Box 19, Folder 2073)
        - Neil, Stephen Charles (Box 19, Folder 2074)
        - Nelson, Daniel (Box 19, Folder 2075)
        - Nerinckx, Charles (Box 19, Folder 2076)
        - Nesbit, Robert (Box 19, Folder 2077)
        - Nettleton, Asahel (Box 19, Folder 2078)
        - Netsvetov, Iakov (Box 19, Folder 2079)
        - Neumann (Box 19, Folder 2080)
        - Neuner, Joseph (Box 19, Folder 2081)
        - Nevius, John Livingstone (Box 19, Folder 2082)
        - New, Charles (Box 19, Folder 2083)
        - Newbigin, (James Edward) Lesslie (Box 19, Folder 2084)
        - Newcomb, Harvey (Box 19, Folder 2085)
        - Newell, James E. (Box 19, Folder 2086)
        - Nowell, Maria (Box 19, Folder 2087)
        - Newell, Samuel and Harriett (Box 19, Folder 2088)
        - Newman, Francis William (Box 19, Folder 2089)
        - Newton, John (Box 19, Folder 2090)
        - Ngizaki, Gapenno (Box 19, Folder 2091)
        - Nicolas of Japan (Box 19, Folder 2092)
        - Nokolai, Kasatkin (Box 19, Folder 2093)
        - Nicolai, Philipp (Box 19, Folder 2094)
        - Nicolas of Cusa (Box 19, Folder 2095)
        - Nicholas I (Box 19, Folder 2096)
        - Nicholas Ziorov (Box 19, Folder 2097)
        - Nicholas IV (Girolamo Masci) (Box 19, Folder 2098)
        - Nicolayson John (Box 19, Folder 2099)
        - Nida, Eugene A. (Box 19, Folder 2100)
        - Nielsen, Alfred Julius (Box 19, Folder 2101)
        - Niijima, Jo (also known as Nishima, Joseph Hardy) (Box 19, Folder 2102)
        - Nikon ho Metanoeite (Box 19, Folder 2103)